<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Modern notes manager for macOS and iOS</title><link>https://fsnot.es/</link><description>Recent content on Modern notes manager for macOS and iOS</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:45:00 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fsnot.es/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>FSNotes 7 for macOS and iOS</title><link>https://fsnot.es/fsnotes7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:45:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://fsnot.es/fsnotes7/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="fsnotes-700-release-notes"&gt;FSNotes 7.0.0 Release Notes&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi, friends!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A huge amount of work has gone into FSNotes 7. The editor has been sped up, the code highlighting engine has been rewritten, even more attention has been paid to the UI, and many other things you asked for made it into this release:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center; margin: 50px 0"&gt;
 &lt;img src="https://fsnot.es/img/fsnotes7/FSNotes7_macOS_iOS.webp" style="display: inline; margin: 0 auto; width: 600px; max-width: 600px"/&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Release Date:&lt;/strong&gt; January 19, 2026&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Platforms:&lt;/strong&gt; macOS 12+, iOS 18+&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>FSNotes 6 for iOS</title><link>https://fsnot.es/fsnotes6-for-ios/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 18:23:15 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://fsnot.es/fsnotes6-for-ios/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="meet-fsnotes-6-for-ios"&gt;Meet FSNotes 6 for iOS!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="new-design"&gt;New design&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The biggest design change in the history of the program. The new FSNotes adheres even more to Apple&amp;rsquo;s human interface guidelines. Branded icons, menus, toolbars, headers, animations and smooth transitions. Everything has become closer to the familiar Apple system programs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to give a huge thanks to my friend Dylan Seeger for his valuable advice. Thanks to his ticketing, you see this update like this.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>FSNotes 6 for macOS</title><link>https://fsnot.es/fsnotes6-for-mac/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 08:52:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://fsnot.es/fsnotes6-for-mac/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="all-about-fsnotes-6"&gt;All about FSNotes 6&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s been a long time since the last big issue. The covid ended, the war began, I moved to Lviv, this post I am writing with no light at all. A huge series of events, among which it would seem there is no place for development. But luckily life hasn&amp;rsquo;t stopped and today I am happy to present you a new major update for macOS, on which I&amp;rsquo;ve been working since May.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>FSNotes 5 for iOS</title><link>https://fsnot.es/fsnotes5-for-ios/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 18:23:15 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://fsnot.es/fsnotes5-for-ios/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="meet-fsnotes-5-for-mobile"&gt;Meet FSNotes 5 for Mobile!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="interface"&gt;Interface&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Transitions between controllers have become smoother and more native, this applies to both the main screen and the editor. Access to the settings has become easier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To call up the action menu above the note, just hold your finger on the note (the sidebar must be closed).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://fsnot.es/img/fsnotes5-ios/8822c62e-16ef-4f4c-b397-55d2d79e86fb.webp" alt=""&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3 id="versioning"&gt;Versioning&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you accidentally erased part of the note, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter. Now at any time you can return to the state until you entered the editor and roll back the changes, and you can also create a new version of the file at any time.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>FSNotes 5 for macOS</title><link>https://fsnot.es/fsnotes5-for-mac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 18:23:15 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://fsnot.es/fsnotes5-for-mac/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="all-about-fsnotes-5"&gt;All about FSNotes 5&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello again! Almost two years have passed since the last major release, time flies by. Last summer, I pulled up FSNotes for iOS, and now it&amp;rsquo;s the turn of the macOS version of the program. A lot of work was done between 4 and 5, but for now I will focus on the innovations of the five.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The interface of the program has not changed much, but inside this update at least half a hundred bugs have been fixed. Attribute caching makes switching between notes even smoother, and new features will not give a reason to return to the old version of the program.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>